dosearches.com 2017-06-23

# Dosearches.com

### PRIVACY POLICY

Seablue Technology Limited ("us" or "we") operate the website www. dosearches.com. We respects your privacy and we want you to be confident in sharing your information with us. This Website Privacy Statement is designed to inform you of the types of information we collect from users,how we use that information,and the circumstances under which we will share it with third parties. This Website Privacy Statement applies only to the Websites. It does not apply to your use of any other websites (whether or not operated by us),including any websites to which we provide links or websites of our partners or advertisers,or to any activities which are not online.  
Www.dosearches.com takes your privacy earnestly. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

### Anonymous User Information

We collect some anonymous information each time you use our service so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address,referral data,and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with us before we can collect this anonymous information

We do not require you to share information that identifies you personally,such as your name or e-mail address,in order for you to use our service. Our service assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited our service,your search terms,and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Website servers,we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. Our service analyzes the information to examine trends,administer the site,track user’s movement in the aggregate,and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Individual User Information

From time-to-time our website request information from you that may identify you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name,e-mail address,shipping address,and zip code),and demographic information (such as age,gender,occupation,and household income). Our website will not use or disclose your individual user information except as described in this privacy policy.

### This privacy policy only applies to Dosearches

Dosearches.com does not rent,sell,or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Dosearches.com may disclose your Personal Information if Dosearches.com believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Dosearches.com;(b) protect and defend the rights or property of Dosearches.com (including the enforcement of our agreements);or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Dosearches.com services or members of the public.

### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We are committed to protecting your information. We have adopted commercially reasonable technical,administrative,and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss,misuse,unauthorized access,and alteration. Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

### TRANSITIONS FOR BUSINESS

In the event that Dosearches.com goes through a business transition,such as a merger,acquisition by another company,or sale of all or a portion of its assets,Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. Dosearches.com will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Dosearches.com may have prior to such transfer.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Dosearches.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.
